I don't know I'm feeling well defeated
today my kid out for Halloween festivity
and doing anything makes me low-energy
the next few days and that's annoying I
mean that's my own personal that's
annoying but I can deal with because
it's just living life on slow pace and
having to recuperate but being a mom's
like my first job my most important job
and so I can't not do those things but
it still it makes me less mentally
focused on creating a planet that works
for her Brazil just elected someone
who's going to destroy the whole Amazon
rainforest or as much as he can until
the people rise up we're facing an
ecological catastrophes that we've never
before experienced as as a planet
sorry not as a planet as a species
because our planet has dealt with mass
extinction but we've yet to deal with
the extinction of our own species and
that is kind of what we are facing and
why I'm frustrated and defeated is I
have an actual solution to it and I'm
fili
I'm doing is tweet he's getting through
her followers and it's I have like less
than 300 and every time I try something
new to get them like I'll get a bunch in
one day which is awesome but I mean a
bunch being what can that possibly when
I only have 300 total I don't want to
put her followers so I can I don't know
become the next Kim Kardashian I don't
even care that those people want that
like by all means do what you makes you
happy feel like I'm failing and I can
see where I'm inadequate in this role
not in this role because I know that
there is no inadequate in this role but
like if only you folding my brain focus
and I could do work that other people
could do if only I could communicate
this idea in a way that it could go
viral and we can start creating the
solutions that save the world all I can
do is my part which is exactly what I'm
doing from my bed the spoons I have
remaining I'm just frustrated cuz it's
not gonna look anything like what it
looked like in the past I'm not Jesus
I'm not Martin Luther King I'm not like
these figure charismatic figure head not
that you don't want to like say Jesus
let's go figure but like someone who
leads an entire movement it's like and
this is what everyone does and this is
why that's not what this is cuz we can't
wait for that not when the whole system
is gained against them come up with the
solution you still have to have the
personality all of the inner
figured out to be able to get it out in
the world and what we need is solutions
and heroes on a massive scale we don't
need one hero we need 10,000 people
funding funding something so that like I
want it I don't want to be the the sole
leader I want to be one of 10,000 people
funding a technology company that
creates the solutions that we need on
this planet with solutions to be on this
planet we decide that together although
I have many many an opinion and an idea
if we have the tools to collaborate on a
massive scale we could just jump on when
something like the Prophet like
that Brazil elects someone who's going
to destroy the Amazon rainforest and do
something besides petitions and wait for
a leader to rise up for that with
singular movement and have to gain their
own followers of their own and
throne it's like we can't keep
recreating the wheel every time if
everyone has to deal with funding every
new idea has to deal with funding and
marketing and all of that that
goes with the current capitalist system
just to give us a solution that we so
desperately need we're not going to be
able to save ourselves we need to tap
into human well who humans are that
there are lazy ones and there are stupid
ones every different intelligence I say
this is someone who is stupid in many
intelligence and brilliant in others we
can't need people to be on pedestals to
give what they're here to give to the
world we need to meet meet people where
they are and allow them to contribute in
a way that is meaningful to them as an
individual for the betterment of
everyone else
and we can absolutely create those tools
together I should do that